Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Posters, flyers, programs, 1995; RG0055 Series 26; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  - S. Westenhoefer, 10/14/1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Sponsored by JYP and Chesapeake Concerts. 2 posters
- Photographs, 1941-1988; RG0055 Series 27; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes photographs of dancers, 10,000 Maniacs, Lisner cornerstone ceremony, troubadours, Lisner stage, mural curtain by Augustus Tack, President and Mrs. Truman, telethon at Lisner with Perry Como and Robert F. Kennedy, and the radio station in Lisner. They range in date from 1941-88.
  Formerly ACC # 497.
  - Photo (from a painting) - Abram Lisner, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Photo - "10,000 Maniacs", 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
    autographed
  - Photo-Ballerina, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - Photo-Dancers, Santiago, Chile, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.4)
  - Photo-Dancers, Santiago, Chile, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - Photo-Dancers, Santiago, Chile, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.6)
  - Photo-Dancers, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.7)
  - Photo-Dancers, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Photo-Ballerinas-Violette Verdy, Edward Villella, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Photo-Lisner Auditorium before completion, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Photo-The Traveling Troubadours-Lisner Auditorium, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Photo-Students standing outside Lisner Auditorium, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Photo-Lisner Auditorium stage and seating, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
  - Photo-Lisner Auditorium Interior with Glass Fiber mural curtain "The Spirit of Creation" by Augustus Tack, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.7)
  - Photo-Lisner Auditorium Glass Fiber mural curtain "The Spirit of Creation" by Augustus Tack, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.8)
  - Photo-Historian and Mrs. Arnold Toynbee joined President Carroll, Miss Lucile Graham, and Poet Arnold Curnow at Lisner Auditorium to hear others in the Lecture series, 04/1961 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Photo-President Truman and Mrs. Truman, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Photo-Telethon at Lisner Auditorium from left to right, Perry Como, Robert F. Kennedy, Eddie Fisher, and Edward Kennedy, 02/17/1968 (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Photo-Laying the cornerstone at Lisner Auditorium, Dr. Marvin, Sec. Harry C. Davis, Mr. Leon Tobriner?, Henr P. Erwin, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
  - Photo-Radio Studio in Lisner Auditorium, 1944 ca. (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
- Programs, RG0055 Series 28; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Washington Performing Arts Society and Washington National Symphony programs.
  Formerly ACC# 498.
  This series is unprocessed, please ask staff for assistance.
- Programs and flyers, 1995; RG0055 Series 29; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs and flyers from October 1995.
  Formerly ACC#502
  - program: Antologia de Zarzuelas, 10/29/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Of Human Rights
  - Trisha Brown Dance Company, 10/20/1995-10/21/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: WPAS. 2 programs, 2 posters
  - Victor Borge, 10/25/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    2 programs, 2 invitations
  - Program: University Symphonic Band, 10/24/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: Music Dept.
  - Program: Henry Rollins 2.13.61 Under Construction, 10/27/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: Music Dept. 2 programs
  - Program: "The Gathering", 11/01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sponsor: Quali-Teev. 2 programs
  - Program: Mr. and Mrs. America Body Building Championships, 10/28/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Sponsor: Potomac Valley Association of the AAU. 2 programs
  - Manual: SmartSuite 96, 10/31/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sponsor: Lotus
- Posters, 1995; RG0055 Series 30; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes performance posters from Lisner auditorium from August-November 1995.
  Formerly ACC#513
  - Program and Posters: Kronos Quartet, 11/11/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsors: Concert Society at Maryland and Lisner Auditorium. 1 program, 4 posters
  - Program: University Wind Ensemble, 11/12/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: Music Dept. 2 programs. Missing as of June 2002
  - Poster: Willy Barcena, 11/07/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: Program Board
  - Program: Sentimental Journey, 11/04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: DC Barbershop Harmony Society. 2 Programs. Missing as of June 2002
  - Poster: Inti-illimani, 11/19/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: J. Yates Productions and Lisner Auditorium
  - Poster: Cosi Fan Tutti (Women are Like That), 08/20/1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sponsor: Opera International
  - Poster: Kankouran, 09/02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Poster: Rich Mullins, 11/05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sponsor: International Bible Society. 2 posters. Missing as of June 2002
  - Poster: Grover Washington, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Dated 110/22. Sponsor: Audiences for the Arts. Missing as of June 2002
- Appointment books, contracts, 1977-1983; RG005 Series 31; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes appointment books and contracts from 1977-83.
  Formerly ACC#529
  - Day Planner, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 02/03/1983-07/16/1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 08/16/1983-12/31/1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mission to the Eighties, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Contract?
- Schedule, program, pamphlet, 1995; RG0055 Series 32; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Fall 1995 schedule, Georgetown day school graduation program, Lisner info pamphlet from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#546
  - Fall 1995 schedule (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lisner information pamphlet, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    10 copies
  - Georgetown Day School Graduation Program, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Posters, 1996; RG0055 Series 33; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series includes performance posters from Lisner auditorium from March -April 1996.
  Formerly ACC#547
  - Poster: The Fourth Annual Korean Friendship Night, 04/08/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Korean Student Association
  - Poster: Mitch Frohman, 10/22/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: Audiences for the Arts. Autographed
  - Poster: Tracy Chapman, 03/22/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: Cellar Door. Autographed
  - Poster: Flying Karamazov Brothers- "Club Sandwich", 04/01/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: Gesundheit Institute
  - Poster and Program: Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC- "Campaign Crazy", 03/29/1996-03/30/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: Federal City Performing Arts Association
  - Poster: Tale of Princess Kaguya, 03/11/1996-03/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sponsor: Kageboushi Theatrical Company
  - Poster: Joan Baez, 03/16/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Sponsor: Audiences for the Arts. 2 Posters
- Posters, 1992-1996; RG0055 Series 34; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes performance posters from Lisner auditorium from 1992-96.
  Formerly ACC#548
  - Flyer: The Pan Masters, 04/09/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Washington Performing Arts Society. Missing as of June 2002.
  - Poster: The Flying Karamozov Brothers, 04/01/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: ICM Artists
  - Poster: Multi Kulti, 06/13/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: District Curators. 3 Posters
  - Poster: No Time Players, 04/27/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Pomo Afro Homos, 12/04/1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: Washington Performing Arts Society. Missing as of June 2002
- Posters, 1991-1994; RG0055 Series 35; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes performance posters from Lisner auditorium from 1991-94.
  Formerly ACC#569
  - Nigeria National Dance Troupe, 07/11/1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Black History Celebration, 02/10/1992-03/12/1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adrian Belew, 05/14/1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 03/24/1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bodeans, 05/18/1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Billy Pilgrim, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Martin Luther King Convocation, 01/24/1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kankouran, 09/03/1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Phish, 03/07/1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Programs, postcards, 1995-1996; RG0055 Series 36; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs and postcards for performances from Dec. 1995-Mar. 1996.
  Formerly ACC#570
  - Russ Freeman and Rippingtons, 03/23/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Steve Loves NY Express Roller Dance Company, 03/16/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Allen and Warren Jones, 03/17/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A Cannonball Adderly Celebration, 03/09/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bale Folclorico da Bahia, 03/15/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Charlie Byrd, 02/03/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Taketori Monogatari, 03/11/1996-03/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Law Revue, 03/02/1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Cuban National Folkloric Dance Ensemble, 02/23/1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Duke Ellington Show Choir, 02/16/1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 175th Anniversary Charter Day Convocation, 02/09/1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Renee Fleming, 03/22/1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Programs, 1996; RG0055 Series 37; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series performance programs for May 1996.
  Formerly ACC#573
  - Gladys Stern Tribute, 05/15/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Teach-In 2, 05/10/1996-05/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hooding Ceremony, 05/15/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GSEHD Awards Ceremony, 05/18/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Elliott School Awards, 05/18/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1996 Season (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Doctor of Medicine Degree Program, 05/19/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Programs, pamphlets, tickets, 1946-1991; RG0055 Series 38; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs, pamphlets, and tickets. It also includes a tax certificate for Lisner from Nov. 5, 1946. These records range in date from 1946-91.
  Formerly ACC#580
  - Federal Tax Admissions Certificate for Lisner Auditorium, 11/05/1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tickets from Lisner Auditorium, 1964-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program-Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Program-Benjamin Britten's "The Turn of the Screw;" Washington National Symphony Concert Season, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Valentine Day Massacre; The National Ballet; Ronald Turini Pianist; Joe Cocker and the Hamilton Face Band; Commencement of Frank W. Ballou High School
  - Program-Washington Performing Arts Society presents "Julian Bream", 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Program-The Philippine Nurses Association of Metropolitan Washington presents "Philippine Night", 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Programs-The National Ballet "The Nutcracker;" GWU Dance Company "Dance", 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    The Washington Ballet; The American Bach Foundation et al present "Mari-Elizabeth Morgan, pianist;" "Roy Radin's Vaudeville '75" (signed by Beverly Sills, Godfrey Cambridge, Donald O'Connor, Johnnie Ray), "Roy Radin's Vaudeville '76" (signed by George Jessel, the Ink Spots)
  - Program-The Washington Ballet, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Programs, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    The Washington Ballet "Nutcracker;" The Harvard Club presents "John Harvard: Movie Star;" IFBB Mr. North America, Junior Mr. America
  - Program-The Washington Ballet "Nutcracker", 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Signed
  - Program-GWU Dance Production Groups present "Laser Dance", 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Program-The Washington Ballet 10th Anniversary Season, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Program-The Washington Bach Consort 2nd Annual Bach Birthday Bash, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Program-Washington Concert Opera (signed); Third Annual World Folk Music Association Benefit Concert, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Program-Washington Concert Opera, Richard Strauss' "Ariadne Auf Naxos", 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Programs, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Little Man Tate (small & large, 2 copies each); National Heritage Fellowships Celebration and Concert; Lisner at Noon presents "Beverly Cosham;" Creole Families: Louisiana Zydeco & Jazz, The Ardoin Family Band; Poets, Politicians, and other Storytellers; Live in Concert: Chick Corea Elektric Band and Michael Hedges (2 copies); The D'Addario Foundation for the Performing Arts presents "Paco Pena Flamenco Company;" Disability Awareness Week (2 copies); "I Didn't Hear That Color" (2 copies)
  - Programs, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Patrick Hayes, Friday Morning Music Club Concerts; Charlin Jazz Society in association with Jazz 90 presents "The Wonderful World of Louis Armstrong: A 90th Birthday Salute to Satchmo!" Christianity in Crisis New Hope; The National Dance Theatre of Zaire with the Isiga Dancers in "NKENGE;" Andre Watts, pianist; An Evening with Bobby Short; The Last Supper at Uncle Tom's Cabin "The Promised Land" with the Julius Hemphill Sextet; An Evening with Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis; Armenian Students Association presents "Charles Aznavour;" Lisner Auditorium advertisement; Connection II & Geoz presents "Los Fronterizos"
  - Lisner Auditorium postcard, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Posters, pamphlets, flyers, 1992-1996; RG0055 Series 39; 1.75 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes posters, pamphlets, and flyers from 1992-96.
  Formerly ACC#628
  - Vivre- To Live; One Exclusive Performance in America, 10/27/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bo Deans Go Slow Down, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Korean Women's Musical Drama, 09/18/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Keiko Matsui Dream Walk, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Forever, For Love and For Life- Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 10/21/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Griot New York, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    2 copies. Dated June 12-13
  - City at Peace- "WHO's to Blame", 11/14/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A Little Night Music, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Dated March 9 to 11
  - Michael Nyman Live, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ottmar Liebert and Luna Negra - The Hours Between Night and Day, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Songs of Peace and Protest: A Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King, 01/17/1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Solo Piano Concert: George Winston, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    2 copies. Dated December 16
  - Handel's Messiah, 12/09/1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Dream in Action, 01/15/1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Heart Strings; The Aids Memorial Quilt and You, 01/09/1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - In the Tradition; Stories, Myths, and Legends, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Harry Connick Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Dated July 3
  - Vigen: 45th Anniversary, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Dated September 7
  - La Boheme, 08/02/1996-08/04/1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Performances on August 2 and 4
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington D.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    5 copies, for varied dates
  - Jerry McGuire, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Glykeria, 10/06/1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Koniaya (The Wedding), 08/31/1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Queen of Morna- with a voice to melt the soul, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    2 copies. Dated November 9
  - Washington Concert Opera, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    3 copies. Dated November 1 and 3
  - 20 Years of Progress, 10/04/1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cleo Laine and the John Dankworth Group, 10/24/1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Tigers and Pussycats: Sources of Growth in Asia and Europe", 11/06/1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Maru Montero Dance Company, 10/05/1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - University Wind Ensemble Fall Concert, 11/12/1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hutchinson New Compositions Concert with Contemporary Music Forum, 10/27/1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - One Exclusive Performance in America, 10/27/1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harvest of Harmony, 11/02/1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Souls Le Haut Patronage de Line Renaud, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Marina, 11/23/1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Who's to Blame, 11/14/1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Christmas Revels, 12/06/1996-12/08/1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - A Solo Piano Concert- George Winston, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Koniaya - (The Wedding), 08/31/1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Olodum, 09/21/1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ozulumba, 08/1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - La Boheme, 08/02/1996-08/04/1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    2 copies. Performances on August 2 and 4
  - The Sixth Season, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gay Men's Chorus, 10/31/1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - University Symphonic Band- Halloween Concert, 10/31/1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Georgetown Day School Graduation, 06/08/1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Grand Evening of Talent Program, 06/10/1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Rafael Puyana - Harpsichordist, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Nutcracker, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    2 copies. Dated December 20
  - Vigen: 45th Anniversary, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mock the Vote, 10/19/1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Washington Concert Opera, 09/17/1996 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Electrified, Amplified, and Deified, 11/09/1996-11/16/1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Opera International - La Boheme, 08/02/1996-08/04/1996 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Saint Andrew Kin Dae-Gun, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Sumpang Mahal Zarzuela and Musicale Extravaganza, 06/13/1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The National Heritage Fellowships, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Summer Showcase - Gay Men's Chorus, 07/05/1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Russian Festival Concert, 06/15/1996 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Convocation, 10/18/1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Korean Women's Musical Drama, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Science and Engineering Apprentice Program, 06/17/1996 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Programs, pamphlets, 1996; RG0055 Series 40; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs and pamphlets from 1996.
  Formerly ACC#633
  - University Singers Spring Concert, 04/20/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Department of Music
  - The Washington Ballet, 04/20/1979-04/21/1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: The Washington Ballet. Signed program
  - Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 04/12/1996-04/13/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: WPAS and Lisner auditorium. 2 copies
  - Yom Ha'Atzmaut, 04/18/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: quali-teev productions. 2 copies
  - Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, 05/05/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Youth Philharmonic, 05/05/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Korean Friendship Night, 04/08/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Sponsor: Korean S.A. 2 copies
- Programs, posters, pamphlets, 1997; RG0055 Series 41; 1 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs, posters, pamphlets, and postcards from 1997.
  Formerly ACC#655
  - Program - Whirling Dervishes, 02/02/1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Foundation for Traditional Studies. 2 copies
  - Program - Verve Jazzfest, 01/22/1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Sponsor: Audience for the Arts. 2 copies
  - Poster - Verve Jazzfest, 01/22/1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: Audience for the Arts. Small Poster. J. Carter
  - Poster - Verve Jazzfest, 01/22/1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: Audience for the Arts. Large Poster. 2 copies. J. Carter
  - Program - New York's Ensemble for Early Music, 02/01/1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: WPAS. 2 copies.
  - Program - National PTA 100th Anniversary, 02/17/1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sponsor: 10 sponsors, primary sponsors Family Education network and National Cable Network. 2 copies.
  - Program - Bale Folclorico de Bahia, 02/22/1997-02/23/1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Sponsor: Lisner auditorium. 2 copies.
  - Program - National Folk Ballet of the Philippines, 02/06/1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sponsor: Foundation for Aid to the Philippines. 2 copies.
  - Atlantic Region Harmony Sweepstakes, 09/1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Sponsor: Contemporary A Capella Society of America. 2 copies.
  - Ute Lemper, 03/11/1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Sponsor: Lisner Auditorium. 2 copies.
  - Jim Brickman, 03/14/1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Sponsor: WASH FM. 2 copies.
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 03/20/1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Sponsor: The Washington Ballet. 2 copies.
  - Law Revue, 03/01/1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Sponsor: Law School. 2 copies.
  - Circque Eloize, 02/15/1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Sponsor: WPAS
  - Rockwell Blake, 03/02/1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Sponsor: Vocal Arts and Lisner Auditorium. 2 copies
  - Washington International Competition, 03/15/1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Sponsor: Friday Morning Music Club. 2 copies
  - Johansen International Competition, 03/15/1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Program - Med Follies, 03/29/1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Sponsor: Med School. 2 Programs
  - Program - Okinawa, 04/01/1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Sponsor: OACCA. 2 Programs
  - Program and Poster - Korean Friendship, 04/03/1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Sponsor: Korean Students Association. 1 program, 2 posters
  - Program - International Night, 04/04/1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Sponsor: Program Board. 1 programs
  - Program - Bhangra Blowout, 04/05/1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Sponsor: South Asian Society. 2 programs
  - Program and Tribute Book - AFT Memorial, 04/09/1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Sponsor: American Federation of Teachers. 4 programs, 2 tribute books
  - Program and Poster - GMC Invitation Dance, 04/11/1997-04/12/1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Sponsor: Federal City Performing Arts. 2 programs, 2 posters
  - Pamphlet - The Earth Charter Gorbachev Event, 04/15/1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Sponsor: Green Cross/Global Green/GW. 2 pamphlets
  - Program - Mikhail S. Gorbachev, 04/15/1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Sponsor: Green Cross/Global Green/GW. 2 programs
  - Poster - Leo Kottke, 04/18/1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Sponsor: Cellar Door. 2 posters
  - Program - University Singers, 04/19/1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Sponsor: GWU Department of Music. 2 programs
  - Poster - Collective Soul, 05/21/1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Sponsor: Cellar Door. 2 BW posters
  - Poster - Collective Soul, 05/21/1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Sponsor: Cellar Door. 1 color poster
  - Program - University Symphonic, 04/30/1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Program - Russian Spring, 05/03/1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Sponsor: Washington Balalaika Society. 2 programs
  - Program and Poster - Sousa National High School Band, 05/10/1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Sponsor: JP Sousa Foundation. 2 programs, 1 poster
  - Program - Noa, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Sponsor: Teev productions. 2 programs. Dated May 14
  - Program - Medical School Commencement, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Sponsor: GWU. 2 programs. Dated May 18
  - Program - Hooding Ceremony, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Sponsor: GWU. 2 programs. Dated May 16
  - Program - GSEHD, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Sponsor: GWU. 3 programs. Dated May 17
  - Program - ESIA, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Program - Washington Ballet School Recital, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Sponsor: Washington Ballet School. 2 programs. Dated May 22
  - Program - Washington Magic Summit, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Sponsor: Summit Foundation. 2 programs. Dated May 23
  - Program - Washington Chamber Symphony, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Sponsor: WCS. 2 programs. Dated June 1
  - Program - Georgetown Day School, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Sponsor: Georgetown Day School. 2 programs. Dated June 8
  - Program - School Without Walls, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Sponsor: School Without Walls. 1 program. Dated June 13
  - Program and Poster - Opera Camerata, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Sponsor: Opera Camerata. 2 programs, 1 libretto. Dated June 14
  - Program - Chinese Music and Dance Performance for the Return of Hong Kong to China, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Sponsor: Yellow River Art Ensemble. 2 programs. Dated June 22
  - Program, Postcard and Poster - Gay Men's Chorus My Buddy, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Sponsor: American Express/Financial Advisors. 2 programs, 4 posters, 4 postcards. Dated June 28
- Posters, programs, 1997; RG0055 Series 42; 1 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes posters, programs, booklet, and brochures from 1997.
  Formerly ACC# 677
  This series has a paper container list in the reading room, please ask staff for assistance.